[
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What is the name of Jon's direwolf?",
        "answer": "Ghost"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What was the name of Robb's direwolf?",
        "answer": "Grey Wind"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What was the name of Sansa's dirework?",
        "answer": "Lady"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What is the name of Arya's dirework?",
        "answer": "Nymeria"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What is the name of Bran's dirework?",
        "answer": "Summer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What was the name of Rickon's dirework?",
        "answer": "Shaggydog"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who is the eldest of the Stark children?",
        "answer": "Robb"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who is the youngest of the Stark children?",
        "answer": "Rickon"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who is the bastard of the Stark family?",
        "answer": "Jon Snow"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What name is given to the bastards of the North?",
        "answer": "Snow"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What name is given to the bastards of the Reach?",
        "answer": "Flowers"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What name is given to the bastards of Dorne?",
        "answer": "Sand"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What name is given to the bastards of the Stormlands?",
        "answer": "Storm"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What name is given to the bastards of the Riverlands?",
        "answer": "River"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What name is given to the bastards of the Vale?",
        "answer": "Stone"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What name is given to the bastards of The Iron Islands?",
        "answer": "Pyke"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What is the name of the Valyrian sword of House Tarly?",
        "answer": "Heartsbane"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What is the name of the Valyrian sword of House Stark?",
        "answer": "Ice"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What two swords does Ice become after it is melted down and reforged?",
        "answer": "Oathkeeper and Widow's Wail"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What is the name of the Valyrian sword of House Mormont?",
        "answer": "Longclaw"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What is the first book in a Song of Ice and Fire?",
        "answer": "A Game of Thrones"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What is the second book in a Song of Ice and Fire?",
        "answer": "A Clash of Kings"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What is the third book in a Song of Ice and Fire?",
        "answer": "A Storm of Swords"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What is the fourth book in a Song of Ice and Fire?",
        "answer": "A Feast for Crows"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What is the fifth book in a Song of Ice and Fire?",
        "answer": "A Dance with Dragons"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who is the king of Westeros during the first book in the series?",
        "answer": "Robert Baratheon"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who is the middle Baratheon brother?",
        "answer": "Stannis"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who is Robert Baratheon's youngest brother?",
        "answer": "Renly"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Whom did Robert Baratheon take the throne from?",
        "answer": "Mad King Aerys Targaryen II"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who is the wife of Robert Baratheon?",
        "answer": "Cersei Lannister"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What is the name of the woman that Robert Baratheon laments over?",
        "answer": "Lyanna Stark"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What is Ned Stark's first name?",
        "answer": "Eddard"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Whom was Catelyn Stark supposed to marry instead of Ned?",
        "answer": "Ned's older brother Brandon Stark"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What is the name of Ned Stark's younger brother?",
        "answer": "Benjen Stark"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What was Catelyn Stark's maiden name?",
        "answer": "Tully"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who is the oldest of Ned and Catelyn Stark's children?",
        "answer": "Robb Stark"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who is the second oldest of Ned and Catelyn Stark's children?",
        "answer": "Sansa Stark"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who is the third oldest of Ned and Catelyn Stark's children?",
        "answer": "Arya Stark"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who is the fourth oldest of Ned and Catelyn Stark's children?",
        "answer": "Brandond (Bran) Stark"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who is the youngest of Ned and Catelyn Stark's children?",
        "answer": "Rickon Stark"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Whom does Ned claim is his bastard son?",
        "answer": "Jon Snow"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who wields the axe that beheaded Ned Stark?",
        "answer": "Ser Ilyn Payne"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "After Ned Stark's death, who is declared King in the North?",
        "answer": "Robb Stark"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What is the name of the uncle at whose wedding Robb Stark is murdered?",
        "answer": "Edmure Tully"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who was the bride of Edmure Tully?",
        "answer": "Roslin Frey"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who is the ward of Ned Stark and treated as a brother to to the Stark children?",
        "answer": "Theon Greyjoy"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What animal is on the coat of arms of House Stark?",
        "answer": "Direworld"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What mantra is on the coat of arms of House Stark?",
        "answer": "Winter is Coming"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What animal is on the coat of arms of House Baratheon?",
        "answer": "A Stag"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What animal is on the coat of arms of House Lannister?",
        "answer": "A Lion"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who is the red-haired wildling woman that Jon Snow breaks his vows with?",
        "answer": "Ygritte"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What is the sigil on the banner of House Targaryen and what what color is it?",
        "answer": "Red dragon"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What is the sigil on the banner of House Blackfyre and what what color is it?",
        "answer": "Black dragon"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What animal is on the sigil of House Mormont?",
        "answer": "Bear"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What is the sigil of House Bolton?",
        "answer": "A flayed man"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who is the Bastard of Bolton?",
        "answer": "Ramsay Bolton"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What is on the sigil of House Glover?",
        "answer": "A fist"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "In what land does House Tully reside?",
        "answer": "Riverrun"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who is Catelyn Stark's sister?",
        "answer": "Lysa Arryn"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who is Lysa Arryn's deceased husband?",
        "answer": "Jon Arryn"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Where does Lysa Arryn live?",
        "answer": "At the Eyrie"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who succeeds Robert Baratheon on the Iron Throne?",
        "answer": "Joffrey Baratheon"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who tells Catelyn Stark that the knife used in the attempted murder of Bran belonged to Tyrion Lannister?",
        "answer": "Petyr Baelish"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "How does Tyrion Lannister prove his innocence of the attempted murder of Bran Stark?",
        "answer": "Trial by combat"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who is Tyrion Lannister's champion at trial by combat?",
        "answer": "Bronn"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Whom does Robb Stark send to forge an alliance with Balon Greyjoy?",
        "answer": "Theon Greyjoy"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Whom does Robb Stark send to forge an alliance with Renly Baratheon?",
        "answer": "His mother, Catelyn Stark"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Where is the ancestral seat of the Baratheon House?",
        "answer": "Storm's End"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Whom does Catelyn Stark send Jaime Lannister with to King's Landing in an attempt to exchange Jaime for her daughters?",
        "answer": "Brienne of Tarth"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "To what gods did Jon Snow swear his Night's Watch oath?",
        "answer": "The Old Gods"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "In front of what kind of tree does Jon Snow swear his Night's Watch oath?",
        "answer": "A Heart Tree"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What is the name of the fierce wildling woman that Jon Snow falls in love with?",
        "answer": "Ygritte"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What was Jon Snow's birth name?",
        "answer": "Aegon Targaryen"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What was the name of the High Commander that Jon Snow served on the Night's Watch?",
        "answer": "Jeor Mormont"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who is the lordling that Jon Snow befriends on the Night's Watch?",
        "answer": "Samwell Tarly"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who is the Master of Arms for the NIght's Watch?",
        "answer": "Alliser Thorne"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who is called the Old Bear?",
        "answer": "Jeor Mormont"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "How is Jeor Mormont killed?",
        "answer": "In a mutiny"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What is Yoren's job in the Night's Watch?",
        "answer": "Recruiter"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who disguises Arya to look like a boy to sneak her out of King's Landing?",
        "answer": "Yoren"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who is Samwell Tarly's father?",
        "answer": "Randyll Tarly"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Prior to the Night's Watch, where is Samwell Tarly's home located?",
        "answer": "Horn Hill"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who is the former Commander of the City Watch and sent to join the Night's Watch at The Wall?",
        "answer": "Janos Slynt"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who exiles Slynt to the Night's Watch?",
        "answer": "Tyrion Lannister"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "After failing to follow any orders given to him, who publicly executes Janos Slynt?",
        "answer": "Jon Snow"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who is the Master of Arms at Castle Black?",
        "answer": "Alliser Thorne"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who deserted the Night's Watch and later become the King-beyond-the-wall?",
        "answer": "Mance Rayder"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who unites all of the wildlings together to attack the Wall?",
        "answer": "Mance Rayder"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who disguised Mance Rayder to save his life?",
        "answer": "Melisandre"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What does Jon order Mance Rayder to do?",
        "answer": "Rescue Arya Stark"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What is the name of daughter of the steward that Arya Stark pretends to be to avoid capture?",
        "answer": "Jeyne Poole"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Whose help does Mance Rayder enlist to rescue Arya Stark?",
        "answer": "Theon Greyjoy's"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who sends a letter to Jon claiming to have capture Mance Rayder and is keeping him prisoner?",
        "answer": "Ramsay Bolton"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who becomes Jon Snow's spearwife?",
        "answer": "Ygritte"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What is the name of Craster's home?",
        "answer": "Craster's Keep"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "How many wives does Craster have?",
        "answer": "19"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who kills Craster in the Mutiny at Craster's Keep?",
        "answer": "Karl Tanner"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who is Gilly the wife of?",
        "answer": "Craster"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What is the sex of Gilly's baby?",
        "answer": "male"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "With whom does Gilly flee Craster's Keep?",
        "answer": "Samwell Tarly"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who is Mance Rayder's wife?",
        "answer": "Dalla"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who is the sister of Mance Rayder's wife?",
        "answer": "Val"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Which Wildling warlord and his people is Val sent to bring to the Wall?",
        "answer": "Tormund"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who is often called Rattleshirt?",
        "answer": "the Lord of Bones"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who glamours the Lord of Bones so that he replaces Mance Rayder in his execution?",
        "answer": "Melisandre"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who is the First Steward of the Night's Watch based at Castle Black?",
        "answer": "Bowen Marsh"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Which member of the Night's Watch is known for his melancholy temperament and sarcastic wit?",
        "answer": "Eddison Tollett or Dolorous Edd"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What two nicknames is the Wildling Tormund known by?",
        "answer": "Tormund Giantsbane and Tormund Thunderfist"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "How many animals is Varamyr capable of controlling?",
        "answer": "Six"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who is often called Littlefinger?",
        "answer": "Petyr Baelish"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What was Petyr Baelish's title in King's Landing?",
        "answer": "Master of Coin"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Whom does Petyr Baelish marry and then murder?",
        "answer": "Lysa Arryn"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What does Petyr Baelish declare himself after Lysa Arryn's death?",
        "answer": "Lord Protector of the Vale"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who is called the Spder?",
        "answer": "Varys"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What role does Varys fullfil in King's Landing?",
        "answer": "Master of Whispers"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What name is given to the bastards of the Reach?",
        "answer": "Flowers"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What name is given to the bastards of the Reach?",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What name is given to the bastards of the North?",
        "answer": "Snow"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What name is given to the bastards of the Iron Islands?",
        "answer": "Pyke"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What name is given to the bastards of the Riverlands?",
        "answer": "Rivers"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What name is given to the bastards of the Vale?",
        "answer": "Stone"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What name is given to the bastards of the Westerlands?",
        "answer": "Hill"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What name is given to the bastards of the Stormlands?",
        "answer": "Storm"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What name is given to the bastards of Dorne?",
        "answer": "Sand"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Which house is a direct vassal of House Baratheon?",
        "answer": "Stokesworth"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who does Robert Baratheon dream of killing every night?",
        "answer": "Rhaegar Targaryen"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who shot Hoster Tully's funeral pyre?",
        "answer": "Brynden Tully"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who kept missing Hoster Tully's funeral pyre with flaming arrows?",
        "answer": "Edmure Tully"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who says they hate crossbows because they take too long to reload?",
        "answer": "Yoren"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "In season 2, who does Tyrion tell Varys he plans on marrying Myrcella to?",
        "answer": "Theon Greyjoy"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "In season 2, who does Tyrion tell Littlefinger he plans on marrying Myrcella to?",
        "answer": "Robin Arryn"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "In season 2, who does Tyrion tell Pycelle he plans on marrying Myrcella to?",
        "answer": "The Martells of Dorne"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "In season 2, who ends up telling Cersei that Tyrion intends on marrying Myrcella to the Martells?",
        "answer": "Maester Pycelle"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who is the king of Westeros when the series begins?",
        "answer": "Robert Baratheon"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "At the end of his trainings, what must an Unsullied kill to prove he has no mercy or weakness?",
        "answer": "A newborn slave child"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who is the liege lord of the Freys before the War of the Five Kings?",
        "answer": "Hoster Tully"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who battled the Mountain during Tyrion Lannister's trial by combat?",
        "answer": "Oberyn Martell"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Whose death was Oberyn Martell trying to avenge during his battle with the Mountain?",
        "answer": "Elia Martell"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who ordered the death of Elia Martell?",
        "answer": "Tywin Lannister"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who wears an eye patch and has a flaming sword?",
        "answer": "Beric Dondarrion"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who chopped of Jaime Lannister's hand?",
        "answer": "Locke"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Which house is Catelyn Stark from?",
        "answer": "Tully"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who is the rightful successor to Robert Baratheon?",
        "answer": "Stannis Baratheon"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who is the youngest brother of Robert Baratheon?",
        "answer": "Renly Baratheon"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who did Brienne first pledge her allegiance to?",
        "answer": "Renly Baratheon"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "After Renly's death, who does Brienne swear allegiance to?",
        "answer": "Catelyn Stark"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What is the name of the inhabitants of The Neck?",
        "answer": "Crannogmen"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Which Valyrian sword was wielded by Visenya Targaryen?",
        "answer": "Dark Sister"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Where did Arya stab the stable boy?",
        "answer": "In the stomach"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who is known as the Lightning Lord?",
        "answer": "Beric Dondarrion"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who threatens to kill Dany and her baby if he doesn't get the golden crown he deserves?",
        "answer": "Viserys Targaryen"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who did Jon execute after his first general meeting as Lord Commander of the Night's Watch?",
        "answer": "Janos Slynt"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "To which castle did Jon Snow assign Janos Slynt?",
        "answer": "Greyguard"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who does Jon order to fetch his sword when he goes to execute Slynt?",
        "answer": "Olly"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Which Lannister died during the destruction of the Great Sept of Baelor?",
        "answer": "Lancel Lannister"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Which Tyrell died during the destruction fo the Great Sept of Baelor?",
        "answer": "Margaery Tyrell"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Whose face did the ghost that killed Renly Baratheon have?",
        "answer": "Stannis Baratheon"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What was the name of the boy that Arya was playing with when Nymeria attacked Joffrey?",
        "answer": "Mycah"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who killed Mycah after Nymeria attacked Joffrey?",
        "answer": "The Hound (Sandor Clegane)"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What type of wine does the merchant use to try to poison Dany?",
        "answer": "Arbor Red"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "How many times has Beric Dondarrion been resurrected?",
        "answer": "6 times"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who resurrects Beric Dondarrion?",
        "answer": "Thoros"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What is the name of Robb Stark's wife?",
        "answer": "Talisa"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What kind of business does Littlefinger own?",
        "answer": "Brothels"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Beside what did Jon Snow take his Night's Watch vows?",
        "answer": "Weirwood tree"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Which chemical was used to destroy Stannis Baratheon's fleet at the Battle of the Blackwater?",
        "answer": "Wildfire"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "To whom is Myrcella betrothed in season 2?",
        "answer": "Trystane Martell"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What is the name of Arya's sword?",
        "answer": "Needle"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "To whom does Jon ask to not revive him?",
        "answer": "Melisandre"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who tells Theon Greyjoy that he is truly lost?",
        "answer": "Ser Rodrik"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Which Direwolf dies in season 1?",
        "answer": "Lady"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who asked Arya to carry him?",
        "answer": "Polliver"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who was the second direwolf to die?",
        "answer": "Grey Wind"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Which house has a sigil of a silver trout?",
        "answer": "House Tully"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What do the people of the Seven Kingdoms call the Free Folk beyond the wall?",
        "answer": "wildlings"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Jon orders Rickon's body to be buried where?",
        "answer": "The crypt of House Stark"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What is the nickname given to Brynden Tully?",
        "answer": "Blackfish"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "In which region was Catelyn Stark when she died?",
        "answer": "The Twins"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who was the Hand of the King before Eddard Stark?",
        "answer": "Jon Arryn"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who was Ros' regular customer at Winterfell?",
        "answer": "Theon Greyjoy"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What is the name of the prostitue that Tyrion has follow him around?",
        "answer": "Shae"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who said Kill me and be cursed. You are no king of mine!",
        "answer": "Richard Karstark"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "What were Tywin Lannister's last words before Tyrion killed him?",
        "answer": "You are no son of mine"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who is Renly Baratheons's lover?",
        "answer": "Loras Tyrell"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "How many men did Theon Greyjoy use to capture Winterfell?",
        "answer": "20"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Which position of the king's small council has the voice of the king?",
        "answer": "the Hand of the King"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who is Daenerys's mother?",
        "answer": "Rhaella"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Before leaving Winterfell, to whom does Jon offer a gift?",
        "answer": "Arya"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who claims his allegiance is to the Realm?",
        "answer": "Lord Varys"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who created the first White Walker?",
        "answer": "The Children of the Forest (Leaf)"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who was Aerys Targaeryn II's Hand?",
        "answer": "Twin Lanninster"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who is Jon Snow's real mother?",
        "answer": "Lyanna Stark"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who was Shagga's father?",
        "answer": "Dolf"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who said Give me Something for the Pain and Let me Die?",
        "answer": "Robert Baratheon"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Where did Lord Commander Mormont die?",
        "answer": "Craster's Keep"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "Who kills Daenerys?",
        "answer": "Jon Snow"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    },
    {
        "category": "Game of Thrones",
        "question": "example question",
        "answer": "example answer"
    }
]